barefootdreams.com 2017-04-17

# Barefoot Dreams® - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

We respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use personal information from you, and with whom we may share it. It is part of our Terms of Use and is binding on you. We may update or otherwise change it from time-to-time without prior notification to you, and you agree to be bound by the changes we make.

You have the option of removing your information from our database at the time of sale so that you do not receive future communications from us. You can also log into your account and change your contact settings, or contact [Barefoot Dreams, Inc. Customer Care](mailto:customercare@barefootdreams.com) by email with the words "Opt Out" in the subject line.

We may contact you using the contact information you provide to us if there is a problem with your order or use of the Site. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact [Barefoot Dreams, Inc. Customer Care](mailto:customercare@barefootdreams.com) by email or call us at **1-855-CO-Z-CHIC (1-855-269-2442).**

**Personal Information We Collect**

Personal information is content that can uniquely identify you, such as your name, date of birth, phone number, email address, mailing address and financial information. It does not include content in a form that does not permit direct association with a specific individual, such as zip codes, area codes or time zones. It also does not include content, such as your user name, that is publically displayed on this Site's blog, or comments, suggestions, ideas or images that you submit to us or post. Please keep in mind that personal or sensitive information you post may be collected and used by others.

We do not knowingly ask for or collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If you believe a child under 13 has submitted personal data to us and you have authority to act on behalf of the child, please contact us to ask to have the information deleted. 

**Cookies and Other Devices**

When you access or otherwise use this Site, we automatically collect and store certain information, such as Internet Protocol addresses, browser type, Internet service providers and date and time of access. Our Site also uses software devices to collect information about Internet use. Cookies may be attached to your web browser to track your shopping cart and to save unique identifiers used to verify your identity and as record numbers in our database. You can set your browser to turn off cookies, but if you do so, our shopping cart system or other parts of this Site may not work properly. If you desire information about cookies or other devices, and your choices regarding them, please contact us.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

We do not sell or rent out your personal information, and, except as set out in this Privacy Policy, we do not share it with others.

We use your personal information to operate this Site, to deliver products and services you have requested, to manage your account, and to provide customer support. You agree we may also use your personal information: (i) to research and analyze your interest in our products and services or products and services offered by others, (ii) to communicate with you about our products or services or those of others that may be of interest to you, (iii) to develop and display content and advertising customized to your interests, (iv) to monitor compliance and enforce our Terms of Use and other terms and conditions on this Site, (v) to verify eligibility and deliver contest prizes, and (vi) to carry out activities described to you and agreed by you when we collect it.

We may use your financial and payment information to process payments, protect you against possible fraudulent transactions, enroll you in programs you select, and prequalify you for credit or other offers that may be of interest to you. We may use personal information you submit in applying for a position with us to communicate with you and evaluate your application. We may share your information with providers retained by us to collect, maintain or evaluate applicants’ information. We may retain your information for possible future openings.

We may disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary (i) to conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal proceedings involving us, our affiliates or the Site; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights and property of our affiliates; or (c) to act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Site, or the public.

**Security Measures**

This Site has security measures in place to safeguard personal information, including but not limited to Verisign's highest level of SSL data encryption and a digital certificate to verify your identity and confirm online transactions, such as the transfer of personal data and credit card purchases. These measures are designed to protect against, but are not a guarantee against, loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized access or disclosure of personal information.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. You agree to immediately notify us of activities detrimental to your interests, our interests or the interests of any third party that occur in your account or using your password, whether or not authorized by you.

**Servers and Data Location**

To best of our knowledge, the servers on which your data will be stored and processed are in the State of California, U.S.A. By submitting personal information to us, you agree that it may be stored and processed on servers located outside the European Economic Area (EEA). If you are within the EEA, you consent to your personal data being exported and stored and processed on any of our servers in any location.

**California Privacy Rights**

In addition to other rights described in this Privacy Policy, if you are a resident of the State of California who has provided us with personal information to obtain products or services for personal, family or household use, you have the right to request and receive, once each calendar year, information we have shared with others for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information includes the categories of personal information we have shared and the names and addresses of the third parties with whom we have shared it in the immediately preceding calendar year. To receive this information, please contact [Barefoot Dreams, Inc. Customer Care](mailto:customercare@barefootdreams.com) by email with “California Privacy Information Request” in the subject line.
